koreanmovie.com 2013-04-30

# Korean News, Movies, Dramas, Actors, Actress Search Result Page - koreanmovie.com

Privacy Policy koreanmovie.com & Ganges Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy when you use koreanmovie.com, which is comprised of (i) koreanmovie.com website, currently located at www.koreanmovie.com (and/or any successor or additional website(s) owned or operated by or for koreanmovie.com); (ii) koreanmovie.com syndication network (which includes third party websites); (iii) koreanmovie.com client, a downloadable application to upload, download and view content (the "koreanmovie.com Client"); (iv) the servers operated by or on behalf of koreanmovie.com; and/or (v) any other technology and/or services that koreanmovie.com provides its users. The following Privacy Policy was prepared to inform you of the information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information.

It is very important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms set out in our Privacy Policy, please do not use koreanmovie.com Service.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will advise you that changes have been made by posting a notice on our website. Your use of koreanmovie.com Service constitutes your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy, as may be amended or revised by us, and you are advised to consult our Privacy Policy regularly for any changes (revisions will be reflected by the "last update" notation below).

If you have any questions regarding koreanmovie.com's policies or practices relating to privacy, please direct them to contact@koreanmovie.com.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Jannuary 22, 2008.

Collection and Use of Information

While using koreanmovie.com Service you may, among other things, gather information on our website, publish and download content, subscribe to one of our services. In doing so, we may collect certain information about you.

We may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding use of koreanmovie.com Service, like the number of users and frequency and manner of usage of koreanmovie.com Service. We may also collect aggregated information regarding the use of our subscription-based service network, such as the extent to which certain features are used. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of our user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. We use this information to better understanding how koreanmovie.com Service is used, and to improve the online experience of our users. This information is not used in a way that will personally identify you.

Similarly, we may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on our website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that our website places onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer hard drive so that we can recognize you the next time you visit us. We use cookies to collect and store some information about you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website. We use this information to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. In the same manner, we may also engage third parties to monitor the usage of koreanmovie.com Service. These third parties may use cookies and web beacons (which collect non-personally identifiable information regarding user behavior on our website) to collect such information, which is also used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. You may disable cookies by following directions on your web browser. Disabling cookies also disables web beacons. You should be aware, however, that by disabling cookies you may be unable to access certain services and features of koreanmovie.com Service.

We may collect personally identifiable information from you when you seek access to certain portions of koreanmovie.com Service, publish or download content, and/or register for our services. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, physical and e-mail addresses, phone and/or fax numbers, Internet address, type of computer and credit card or other payment information, as well as your preferences and usage patterns. This information may be used to fulfill your requests for services, to communicate with you about your account, to support your online activities, to respond to your questions, to customize your experience and to customize the content or features of koreanmovie.com Service. We may use your personally identifiable information to notify you of changes to koreanmovie.com Service, Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. We may also use your personally identifiable information to personalize your interactive experience on koreanmovie.com Service. For example, if you have given us permission, we may use your information to inform you of other products or services that you may find valuable. We may also use the information you provide to make improvements that better serve our users' needs.

If you prefer not to receive information about additional products and services that we think you may be interested in, you can choose not to receive this information by opting-out when given the opportunity at the point we ask you for your contact information. You may also choose to opt-out after the fact by following the Opt Out instructions provided below.

Disclosure of Information

We may share aggregated statistical information about users of koreanmovie.com Service with third-parties, including our distributors, vendors, actual and potential customers and third-parties that offer products or services for use with koreanmovie.com Service. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

koreanmovie.com will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties, with the following exceptions: 

Security

koreanmovie.com is committed to taking appropriate measures to protect your privacy against unauthorized disclosures. koreanmovie.com uses a variety of secure techniques designed to protect your information.

While we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. As such, we cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your personal information from the threats of tomorrow, or that our security measures are failsafe and not subject to circumvention or unauthorized intrusion. You should also be aware that, despite our best efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of data. 

Third-Party Links

Portions of koreanmovie.com Service may contain links to other third party websites that you may access. These other sites have their own privacy policies, and you should review those policies before following those links. We cannot control the information disclosed at these third-party sites or how that information is used. 

Young Children

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. To best protect your child's privacy, we suggest that you carefully supervise your child's access to the Internet and our website. 

Opt-Out

koreanmovie.com Service provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us regarding products and services in which you may be interested. You will be given this opportunity at the time we request information about you. If you do not opt-out at the time you provide information, but choose to opt-out later, click here to send an email indicating that you no longer wish to receive such communications. Please provide your name and physical and/or email address(es) at which you are receiving the unwanted communications. 

Contact

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us at contact@koreanmovie.com
